game-jungle.com 2011-08-31

# Privacy « Game-Jungle.com

Privacy Policy

Privacy is very important to us. This Privacy Statement will describe the types of information we collect, how we use your information to improve your shopping experience, the limited circumstances under which we might disclose information you provide us and the security efforts we take to safeguard your information.

Here are the types of information Game-Jungle.com gathers.  
You provide information to Game-Jungle.com when you search, purchase products,participate in a contest or questionnaire, sign up for our e-mail newsletters, or communicate with customer service. As a result of those actions, you might supply us with such information as your name, address, and phone number; gender; or e-mail address.

We automatically receive and store certain types of information whenever you visit Game-Jungle.com . For example, like most Web sites, we sometimes use “cookies.” Examples of the information we collect and analyze include the Internet protocol (IP) address used to connect your computer to the Internet; e-mail address; password; computer and connection information such as browser type and version, operating system, and platform; including date and time

We use data collection devices such as “cookies” on certain pages of Game-Jungle.com . “Cookies” are small files placed on your hard drive that assist us in providing customized services. You are always free to decline our cookies if your browser permits, although in that case you may not be able to use certain features on Game-Jungle.com

We might receive information about you from other sources and add it to our account information. We also sometimes receive updated delivery and address information from our shippers or other sources so that we can correct our records and deliver your next purchase or communication more easily.

We may use information on file, and other information we obtain from your current and past activities on Game-Jungle.com . By visiting our site, you agree that we may use personally identifiable information about you to improve our marketing and promotional efforts, to analyze site usage, improve our content and product offerings, and customize Game-Jungle.com‘s content, layout, and services. You agree that we may use your information to contact you and deliver information to you that, in some cases, is targeted to your interests, such as product offerings, and communications relevant to your use of the Game-Jungle.com

We do not sell or rent any personally identifiable information about you to any third party. However, the following describes some of the ways that your personally identifiable information may be disclosed.

Game-Jungle.com does not, generally, manufacture any of the products listed on Game-Jungle.com . We may share our data, including personally identifiable information about you, with these manufacturers when necessary, for example, to complete or ship your order or assist manufacturers with your questions concerning products offered by Game-Jungle.com

We work with business partners and selected vendors to provide you with access to their product offerings or to their online stores  
(ie., the Partners listed on Game-Jungle.com available at Game-Jungle.com – EA Store US, Game-Jungle.com – GameFly Game Rentals, Game-Jungle.com – GamersGate, Game-Jungle.com – JJGames, Game-Jungle.com – VP Games, Game-Jungle.com – GameStop, Game-Jungle.com – EB Games or any of the Game-Jungle.com / Partner Shops ).  
We may share our data, including personally identifiable information about you, with these business partners or selected vendors, and they may use this information to offer you products and/or services that may be of interest to you. If you choose to disclose information to the Partners, place orders, and/or grant them permission to collect information about you, then their use of your information is governed by THEIR APPLICABLE PRIVACY POLICIES. To prevent our disclosure of your personally identifiable information to one of these third parties, you can choose not use their services or order their products. Because we do not control the privacy practices of these third parties, you should evaluate their practices before deciding to use their services or place orders with them for their products.

We may disclose information about you to law enforcement or other government officials as we believe necessary in connection with an investigation of illegal activity that may expose you or us to legal liability.

In addition, Game-Jungle.com may periodically send you information and product promotions via e-mail. You may cancel your subscription to our or thier electronic newsletter or end product related e-mails from Game-Jungle.com at any time by following the instructions contained at the end of every such newsletter or e-mail. You may also elect to remove your e-mail address from our newsletter and e-mail mailing lists by sending us an email.

Game-Jungle.com treats information against loss and unauthorized access. We employ many different security techniques to protect such data from unauthorized access by users inside and outside the company. However, “perfect security” does not exist on the Internet. It is important for you to protect against unauthorized access to your computer.

In the event of unauthorized use of your credit card, you must notify your credit card provider in accordance with its reporting rules and procedures.

If you have any concern about privacy at Game-Jungle.com, please send us a thorough description of your concern. This Privacy Statement may change also, and use of information that we gather now is subject to the Privacy Statement in effect at the time of use. We may e-mail periodic reminders of our notices and conditions, unless you have instructed us not to, but you should check Game-Jungle.com frequently to see recent changes.
